A Finding Aid to the Julia P. Herzberg Papers, 1977-2018, bulk 1987-2011, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1990-2017; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1.6 Linear feet Box 1, 3, 8-9; 13.1 Gigabytes ER0013-ER0027, ER0029
  - "Chilean Women Artists, Feminism and Dissidence" (1998), 1998-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Omni Art" (2004, 2005), Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER0019. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Omni Art" Artists, Digital Photographs, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.037 Gigabytes 48 computer files (Folder ER0019)
  - Cuban Arts Festival (2005), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AFA Proposal, Sculptural Permutations: New Ideas and Forms by Latin American and Latino Artists", 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER0020-ER0024 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
  - M. Chilindron, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.116 Gigabytes 29 computer files (Folder ER0020)
  - E. Neto, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes 4 computer files (Folder ER0021)
  - Y. Capote, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.005 Gigabytes 4 computer files (Folder ER0022)
  - Sicardi Gallery, Munoz and Cardoso, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2002-2005; Archival Resource Key (Folder ER0023)
  - Herzberg AFA Proposal, Digital Presentation, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.037 Gigabytes One digital document (Folder ER0024)
  - "The Drop: Urban Art Fill" (2009), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "NeoHooDoo: Art for a Forgotten Faith" (2008), 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Backyard" (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "Embodied Absence: Chilean Art of the 1970s Now" (2016), 2017; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Frost Art Museum, 2009-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Latin American Photography, Exhibitions, 1994-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - "La Biennale di Venezia" (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Catalina Parra: In Retrospect Lehman College Art Gallery (Feb.-Apr. 1992), circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - Catalina Parra: It's Indisputable Jersey City Museum (Sep.-Dec. 2001), Interview and Essay, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Catalina Parra: It's Indisputable Jersey City Museum (Sep.-Dec. 2001), Research Material, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37-38)
  - Magdalena Fernandez Frost Art Museum (Oct. 2011- Jan. 2012), Archival Resource Key
    - Proposal, Budget, Checklist, circa 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Essay, Outline, circa 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Research Material, circa 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER0025-ER0027. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Magdalena Fernandez, Digital Presentation, 2011; Archival Resource Key; 0.019 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER0025)
    - Magdalena Fernandez Multimedia Bio, Digital Video Recording, circa 2010; Archival Resource Key; 3.82 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER0026)
    - MFA Houston MF Lecture (Jan. 2011), Digital Video Recording, circa 2011; Archival Resource Key; 2.69 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER0027)
    - Catalog, circa 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Lecture, Museum of Latin American Art, Los Angeles (Feb. 27, 2012), circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Monika Weiss: Leukos, Remy Toledo Gallery(Jan.-Feb. 2006), circa 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER0029. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Monika Weiss at Remy Toledo Gallery Installation, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.106 Gigabytes Four computer files (Folder ER0029)
  - Monika Weiss: Sustenazo (Lament II) Washington College, MD, JH Lecture (Mar. 30, 2011), circa 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Monika Weiss: Sustenazo (Lament II) Museo de la Memoria y los Derechos Humanos, Santiago (2012) Frost Art Museum, Miami (2014), Archival Resource Key
    - Santiago, Contracts, Invitation, Schedules, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Santiago, Budget, Funding, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Santiago, Installation, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Santiago and Miami, Catalog, Essay by Adriana Valdés, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Santiago and Miami, Catalog Distribution, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Santiago and Miami, Printed Material, Catalog, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Santiago and Miami, Research Material, circa 2012-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Santiago and Miami, Shipping, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Santiago, Wall Text, Signage, circa 2010-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Santiago, Video Donation, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Miami, Contract, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Miami, Installation, circa 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Miami, Wall Labels, Signage, circa 2013-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Miami, Print Loan, Donation, circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Miami, MW Performance and Lecture (Apr. 2014), circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Professional Files, 2003-2014; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.3 Linear feet Box 1, 3, 8
  Professional files document Herzberg's participation on various committees for the Bronx Museum of Art, including the Galeria Balmaceda 1215 Curatorial Committee. Materials include correspondence; minutes; proposals; press releases; exhibition checklists, announcements, and invitations; draft lectures; artist statements; and clippings. Also included are a detailed inventory of Herzberg's files and construction agreement copies from her Manhattan office.
  - Tentative Alteration Guidelines and Partial File Inventory, circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Galeria Balmaceda 1215 Curatorial Committee, 2003-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bronx Museum, Correspondence, 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bronx Museum, Correspondence and Research, 2010-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Bronx Museum, Correspondence, Research, and Miscellaneous, 2011-2017; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Herzberg Inventory, 2018; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22-23)